(Sheldon:)I may have left
a suggested organizational schematic...
(Sheldon:)...for her bedroom closet.
PENNY:
Leonard?
This is gonna be bad.
(Sheldon:)Goodbye, Honey Puffs. Hello, Big Bran.
(Penny(entering):)You came into my apartment
while I was sleeping?
(Leonard:)Yes, but only to clean.
Really more to organize,
you're not actually dirty, per se.
(Penny:)Give me back my key.
(Leonard:)I'm very, very sorry.
Do you understand how creepy this is?
(Leonard:)Yes, we discussed it at length last night.
In my apartment? While I was sleeping?
(Sheldon:)And snoring.
And that's probably just a sinus infection.
But it could be sleep apnea. You might
wanna see an otorhinolaryngologist.
The throat doctor.
(Penny:)And what kind of doctor
removes shoes from asses?
(Sheldon:)Depending on the depth...
(Sheldon:)...that's either a proctologist,
or a general surgeon.